// this file with store my questions and answers

const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'Who currently holds the spot for the greatest golfer of all time, based on total tournament victories?',
    answers: [
      'Jack Nicklaus',
      'Tiger Woods',
      'Arnold Palmer',
      'Sam Snead'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sam Snead'
  }, 
  {
    question: 'What is an albatross?',
    answers: [
      'Accidentally hitting another player’s ball on the green',
      'Driving onto the fairway of an adjacent hole',
      'Shooting a score of three under par on a single hole',
      'Using the flag as a backboard for your putt'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Shooting a score of three under par on a single hole'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the record for most tour-tournament victories?',
    answers: [
      '82',
      '80',
      '73',
      '64'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '82'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the main difference between red and white stakes?',
    answers: [
      'Red stakes require you to always shoot your second shot from the drop zone. White stakes require it from where your ball went out of bounds',
      'If you can find your ball in red stakes, you can play it without penalty. White stakes require a re-tee plus an additional penalty stroke',
      'Red stakes are red, white stakes are white',
      'There is no difference'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'If you can find your ball in red stakes, you can play it without penalty. White stakes require a re-tee plus an additional penalty stroke'
  },
  {
    question: 'As of 2019, you are allowed to keep the flag in the hole if desired.',
    answers: [
      'True',
      'False'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'True'
  },
  {
    question: 'As of 2018, who holds the record for most Major Tournament victories?',
    answers: [
      'Jack Nicklaus',
      'Tiger Woods',
      'Sam Snead',
      'Arnold Palmer'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Jack Nicklaus'
  },
  {
    question: 'From where does the modern game of Golf originate?',
    answers: [
      'England',
      'Rome',
      'Greece',
      'Ireland'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ireland'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the term ‘Grounding the club’ refer to?',
    answers: [
      'Touching the sand, water, or ground while taking practice swings in a hazard',
      'Anytime your clubs touch the ground',
      'The process of taking divots out of the ground while swinging',
      'Sending your clubs to their room as their punishment for disobeying'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Touching the sand, water, or ground while taking practice swings in a hazard'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a score of par on most courses?',
    answers: [
      '70',
      '72',
      '74',
      '75'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '72'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a golf handicap?',
    answers: [
      'Shooting from tee boxes closer to the pin',
      'Lowering par for players who are really good',
      'An average of your last 20 rounds of golf',
      'Special wheelchairs people use to get around the course'
    ]
  }
]